

KADIR ARSLAN

∘ DETAILS ∘

Izmir, Turkey + 90 3123423162 kadir.arslan0110@outlook.com

∘ HIGHLIGHTS ∘

Customer-focused
Independent
Result-oriented
Self-directed
Learner

∘ LANGUAGES ∘

English

o SKILLS o

Javascript
TypeScript
React
Vue.js
Angular

Laravel

Express.js

Next.js

MongoDB

Node.js

GraphQL

MUI

Tailwindcss

Shopify

Stripe

PROFILE

Overall 6+ years of experience in full stack development.

Delivered services of more than \$900, 000 value for 12 clients for the last 6 years.

Proficient in trending JavaScript/Node.js libraries and frameworks.

Practical experience in adopting the modern development methodologies like Scrum & Kanban.

Always keep to best practices and design patterns.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Full Stack Developer at Thinkerfox, Kocaeli

July 2020 — February 2022

- Designed and developed 20+ front-end and back-end applications utilizing React.j, Node.js, and TypeScript
- Presented and conveyed ideas and designs with 5+ technical teams and 18+ business partners.
- Led architecture, design, and development of 20+ new features.
- Mentored and knowledge-shared with younger colleagues on React and Node.
- Participated in 50+ weekly code reviews to ensure code quality and receive mentoring from senior developers
- Attended 60+ weekly standup meetings to receive weekly tasks and mentorship from senior developers...

Senior Front End Developer at WesterOps, Istanbul

January 2018 — May 2020

- Built the company's time tracking system in which 100+ employees would use on a bi-weekly basis using Google API.
- Developed and managed 10 websites for their business marketing and introduction.
- Constructed a scheduling tool successfully in a form of Gantt chart using React and Material-UI.
- Researched and selected libraries and tools.
- Balanced requirements, UX, and deadlines in order to get most of the business value in a limited time frame.
- Composed scripts with Node.js to parse complex data structures.
- Specialized in Node.js, React, Next.js and GraphQL.

Junior Front End Developer at Thinkerfox, Kocaeli

October 2016 — December 2017

- Delivered 30+ projects of all sizes, creating solutions for consumer services.
- Collaborated with 8 design team members to incorporate visual designs into functional web pages
- Created 4 landing pages to support email marketing campaigns and promotions.
- Pair programmed with 3 engineers, and reviewed team's code to provide additional perspective and catch previously missed errors.
- Tested React components using Jest
- Received mentorship from 4 senior developers while consistently implementing their feedback.

Webpack

Git

INTERNSHIPS

Junior Front End Developer at Tmaxsoft Turkey Istanbul, Istanbul

May 2014 — March 2016

- Developed a Responsive and interactive Login page with Validation using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Bootstrap.
- Implemented the required light weighted data validation, manipulation sorting work as required.
- Learned about API's and How to use CORS(Cross-Origin Resource Sharing)

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science, Istanbul University, Istanbul

March 2012 — September 2016

Graduated with excellency